# FERNANDA ZANELLA ALVES

Email: <u>zanella.fernanda@gmail.com</u> | LinkedIn: <u>Fernanda Zanella Alves</u>

GitHub: <u>zanellafernanda</u> | Portfolio: <u>fernandazanella-portfolio</u>

### **DETAILS**

Porto, Portugal

**SUBJECTS** 

HTML5

CSS3

**JavaScript** 

**NodeJS** 

**MySQL** 

**MongoDB** 

Git

## PROFILE

I am a passionate Junior Web Developer with a focus on Full Stack development. My expertise includes HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript 6+, NodeJS, Express JS, API, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, and React. My interest in technology began with geoprocessing projects that involved automating tasks with Python, and I furthered my skills as a digital traffic manager freelancer for e-commerce. I am currently studying Web Development and have completed several projects utilizing various technologies. I possess strong oral and written communication skills, organizational skills, and critical and creative thinking abilities, making me a valuable addition to any team.

## EXPERIENCE

# **Bootstrap Digital Traffic Manager**

2021 - 2022

JQuery Freelancer

Management of Facebook Ads and Google Ads of three e-commerce. Activities involved creating campaigns, performance analysis, optimizations, and SEO

techniques.

Python Researcher

Express JS 2020 – 2021

Mountain Research Center (CIMO) at Polytechnic Institute of Bragança

The research project "TERRAMATER - Medidas innovadoras de recuperación preventiva en áreas quemadas" was related to soil conservation and management, analyzing historical data, and mapping the potential fire areas and

vulnerabilities.

API 2014 – 2017

Federal University of Technology - Paraná, Campo Mourão, Brazil

The research project subjects were related to soil and water conservation and management, developing hydrological models and maps. The software used were

QGIS, ArcGIS, and Excel.

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### EDUCATION

Português(Native)

The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp

Advanced) 2022 - Currently: Udemy

Inglês (Advanced)

# Espanhol (Advanced) Python

2022 - 2023 Institute for Employment and Vocational Training

Master's degree, Environmental Technology

2012 - 2019 Polytechnic Institute of Bragança, Portugal

**Bachelor's degree, Environmental Engineering** 

2012 – 2019 Polytechnic Institute of Bragança, *Portugal; Federal University of Technology - Paraná*, *Campo Mourão*, *Brazil*.